togetherweearn.com 2015-03-20

# Privacy Policy - Together We Earn

NING, INC. PRIVACY POLICY

Effective: July 20, 2010

Ning, Inc. ("Ning", "we" or "us") is an online service provider that provides a set of services and technology applications that enable users to create their own Networks utilizing our technology platform (the "Ning Platform"). Ning is not involved in the management of Networks on the Ning Platform and is not involved in the decisions relating to the focus of Networks or the Content uploaded or published to Networks using the Ning Platform. These are your Networks and, as a Network Creator, you are responsible for managing them in all respects (including the actions, conduct, and Content of Your Members) in compliance with the [Ning Terms of Service.](http://about.ning.com/legal/tos.php)

We value your privacy, and we want to help make your experience on the Ning Platform as satisfying and safe as possible. We have established this Privacy Policy to explain how Personal Information (as defined below) is collected on the Ning Platform, and how that Personal Information is used and disclosed. "Personal Information" is information that allows a person to directly identify an individual, such as name or email address, and information that we combine directly with such identifying information. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the [Ning Terms of Service.](http://about.ning.com/legal/tos.php) Any capitalized terms not defined herein have the meaning set forth in the [Ning Terms of Service.](http://about.ning.com/legal/tos.php) By using the Ning Platform, you expressly consent to the information handling practices described in this Privacy Policy.
